(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
お誕生日3Dはいしん
Birthday 3D Stream
重大発表もあるわよ
There's also a major announcement
Good evening, my cute students! ちょこー！
Good evening, my cute students! Choco-!
ホロライブ所属、悪魔のバーチャル保健医、癒月ちょこです！
I'm Hololive's demon virtual school nurse, Yuzuki Choco!
ということでね、皆様。本日は癒月ちょこ誕生日2021、お集まりいただきありがとうございます。
So everyone, thank you for gathering for Yuzuki Choco's Birthday 2021 today.
ま、今回はね、このハッシュタグ「#癒月ちょこ誕生日2021」でいっぱいスクショとかね、色々呟いてくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you'd tweet lots of screenshots and stuff with this hashtag, #YuzukiChocoBirthday2021.
よかったらね、もうめちゃめちゃ久しぶり、保健室でも...
If you like, it's been a really long time since I've been in the infirmary...
2週間以上？の3Dなんでね。
It's been over 2 weeks since my last 3D.
よかったらいっぱい呟いてトレンド入りしてくれたら、すごく嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします。
If you could tweet a lot and get it trending, I'd be very happy. Thank you!
たくさんのおめでとうコメント、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for all the happy birthday comments.
はい、ということでね。ま、今回お誕生日ということで色々な企画をね、色々と準備して...
So, since it's my birthday today, I've prepared various segments...
まね、色々重大発表とかもあるので、最後まで楽しんでいっていただけたらすごく嬉しいです。
And there are some major announcements, so please enjoy until the end. I'd be very happy.
そしてね、ま、今日はバレンタインということでね...
Also, since today is Valentine's Day...
皆様、いかがお過ごしですか？
How are you all doing?
ま、バレンタインっていうイメージより、ちょこ先生のお誕生日っていうイメージの方がみんなには強いかな？
I wonder if everyone thinks more of "Choco-sensei's birthday" than "Valentine's"?
ありがとう！おめでとうありがとう！うん。
Thank you! Thanks for the birthday wishes! Yeah.
ままま、今日はね、ま、ちょこのお誕生日ということで...
Anyway, since today is Choco's birthday...
ま、せっかくのお誕生日なんでね、ちょこ、お誕生日ケーキ食べたい！
Since it's a special birthday, Choco wants to eat birthday cake!
までもその前にね、お誕生日だから...
But before that, since it's my birthday...
今日はね、お洒落なディナーも食べたいなってちょこ思うんやけど...
Choco's thinking she'd like to eat a fancy dinner today...
うん、ちょこお腹空いちゃったんだよなって思って。
Yeah, Choco's gotten quite hungry.
お？
Oh?
なんかいる。
Something's there.
あんなところに。
Over there.
美味しそうなダックがいる！
There's a delicious-looking duck!
いやもうこれは、ちょこ北京ダック好きなんだよね。
Wow, Choco actually loves Peking Duck.
ちょっと。
Hey.
ほら、おいで。
Come here.
おいで。
ほら、うまそうさ。
Look, you look tasty.
おいで、ほら、おいで、おいで、おいで、おいで。
Come here, come on, come here, come here...
せーの！あっ！
One, two! Ah!
ねぇちょこ...ねぇちょっと待って待って待って待って...
Hey, Choco... wait, wait, wait, wait...
ちょこに、
Let Choco,
ちょこに食べさせて。
let Choco eat you.
ねえ、
Hey,
ダック！
Duck!
おまえ、おまえ意外と、意外と速いな。
You're... you're surprisingly fast.
ちょっちょっちょ、ちょっと待って。
W-w-w-wait a second.
ちょ、ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って！
Wait... wait a second! Wait!
あれ？
Oh?
あった。
There it is.
うまそうな、私の、ディナー。
My delicious-looking... dinner.
ほら、ほら、ほら、ほらほら。
Come here... come here...
捕まえた！
Caught you!
イーーーーー！
Eeeeeeee!
なんなんだこいつ、なんかうるせえな。
What is this thing? It's so noisy.
ホロライブに来て一番の恐怖！
This is the scariest thing since I joined Hololive!
ちょっと待って、
Wait a minute,
スバルなのこれ？ガチ？
is this Subaru? For real?
当たり前だろ！ガチじゃねえよ。
Of course it is! It's not "for real"!
その帽子見てスバルって気づいてくれよ！
Look at the hat and realize it's me!
何に煮きせん...
What were you going to boil me in...
ごめんごめんごめん、ごめんねスバル。
Sorry, sorry, sorry! I'm sorry, Subaru.
放せスバ！放せスバ！
Let me go, Suba! Let me go!
あ、待って、そんな暴れないで、スバル。
Ah, wait! Don't struggle so much, Subaru.
スバル暴れないで。
Subaru, stop struggling.
わかったわかった、放す放す放す。
Alright, alright. I'll let go, I'll let go.
ありがとうね、ありがとう、ありがとう。
Thank you. Thank you very much.
うん、可愛いねスバル。
Yeah, you're so cute, Subaru.
ありがとう。なんかちょっと格差凄くない？色々。
Thanks... But isn't the gap between us huge? In many ways.
ガチ。
For real.
でも、ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとう！
But Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
ありがとうスバル。
Thank you, Subaru.
わい、わい、わい、わい。
Yay, yay, yay!
ええ子だねスバル。
Good girl, Subaru.
ありがとう、ありがとう。
Thank you, thank you.
ツンツンすんじゃねえ！目刺さってんだよ、目に指がよ。
Don't poke me! You're poking my eye! Your finger's in my eye!
ごめんごめんごめん。
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
え、ちょっと可愛くてさ、つい触りたくなっちゃうから。
Well, you're just so cute, I couldn't help wanting to touch you.
やば。
Yikes.
ちょこ先生なかなか過激な座り方してるけど、それ大丈夫かい？
Choco-sensei, you're sitting in quite a radical way. Is that okay?
なかなか過激な座り方してて、スバルが気まずいんですけど。
It's a pretty radical way to sit. It's making me feel awkward.
ちょっと隠しといてあげるね、ちょこ先生。
I'll try to cover for you, Choco-sensei.
あ、ね、ありがとうスバル。
Ah, thanks, Subaru.
ちょっとコメント欄で「ヤンキー」って言われてるけど、
The comments are calling you a "Yankee" squatting like that...
ヤンキーじゃねえよ！
I'm not a Yankee!
いや立ったらさ、スバル踏んじゃいそうで怖いんだよね、結構。
I'm just afraid I'll step on you if I stand up. Really.
ほら。
See?
ちょっと蹴飛ばさないで！か弱い生き物だから、スバルは。意外にか弱いんだからね。
Hey, don't kick me! Subaru is a fragile creature. Surprisingly fragile, you know!
ごめんねスバル。
I'm sorry, Subaru.
ほら、スバルほら、みんなにちゃんと見てもらいな。ほら。
Look, Subaru. Let everyone get a good look at you. Go on.
「見てもらいな」じゃねえんだよ！
Don't "let everyone see me"!
あ、ちょこ先生の枠のチョコメイトのみなさん、お邪魔してます。
Hello to all the Chocomates in Choco-sensei's stream. Sorry for intruding.
大空スバルです、よろしくお願いします。
I'm Oozora Subaru. Nice to meet you.
までもスバル、
But Subaru,
何？
What?
いやー凄いね。美味しそうな姿になったね、うん。
Wow, you really look delicious in that form.
ま、させられたって言った方が正確なんだけどね、うん。
Well, it's more accurate to say I was *made* to be like this.
だからさ、
So,
あん？
Huh?
ちょこに食べられてみない？
how about you let Choco eat you?
それは無理ですね。ちょっとお辞儀しとくかい？
That's impossible. Should I take a bow instead?
当たり前だろお前！当たり前だろお前！
Of course not! Of course not!
わかったスバル、スバルじゃあ
I get it, Subaru. Then, Subaru,
わかった。
I got it.
あん。
Yeah?
私とゲームして私が勝ったら食べられて。
Play a game with me, and if I win, you get eaten.
それってつまり...
Does that mean...
闇のデスゲームということでですか？
you mean it's a Shadow Death Game?
イエス。
Yes.
ちょこと一緒に、これからジェスチャーゲームをしていただきます。
You're going to play a gesture game with Choco.
ジェスチャーデスゲームだった！？おっしゃ受けて立とうじゃねえか！
A Gesture Death Game?! Fine! I'll take your challenge!
イエス！
Yes!
ルールは簡単。
The rules are simple.
ちょこがこれからジェスチャーをしていくので、スバルはちょこのジェスチャーを当てるだけ。
Choco will perform gestures, and Subaru just has to guess what they are.
なるほどね。
I see.
そう。
Right.
で、スバルが先に3問当てることができたら、スバルの勝ち。
If Subaru gets three questions right first, Subaru wins.
あん。
Okay.
全部で5問あります。
There are five questions in total.
なるほどね、まぁ楽勝じゃないっすか。
I see. Well, this will be an easy win.
そう、スバルが勝ったら、ま、今回は見逃してあげる。
Right. If Subaru wins, well, I'll let you go this time.
なるほどね。
I see.
そうそうそう。
Yes, yes, yes.
ま、待てよ！
Wait, wait a minute!
ちょこ先生が負けたら...ちょっと分が悪すぎますよ、こちら側の！
If Choco-sensei loses... the odds are way too bad for my side!
いやいや、ちょこが負けたら、
No, no. If Choco loses,
スバルを元の姿に戻してあげる。
I'll turn Subaru back into her original form.
あーなるほどね、それは嬉しいね。
Ah, I see! That's a relief.
そうそうそう。
Yes, yes, yes.
その可愛いアヒル姿もちょこはいいんだけどね、
I do like that cute duck form too, though...
おいなめたこと言ってんじゃねえぞてめえ本当に！
Hey! Don't get cocky with me, you!
ほらほら、怒んないのスバル。
Now, now. Don't get angry, Subaru.
お前そんなこと言ってるとお前、胸それ以上ナーフさせてやるぞ本当に！
If you keep that up, I'm going to nerf your chest even more! I mean it!
やめて！これ以上はやめて！胸のナーフ強めにしないでください！
Stop! No more! Please don't make the chest nerf any stronger!
運営さん、ちょこのこれ、あの、もうちょっと薄めのレースにしてください、お願いします。
Management! Please, uh, make the lace a bit thinner on this part of Choco's outfit!
やめとけマジで！やめとけお前、こんなめでたい場で！
Stop it! Seriously, stop it! Not on such a happy occasion!
はい、ということでね、じゃあ早速やっていきましょうかね。
Alright, then. Let's get started right away.
はい。
Okay.
じゃあスバル、これからちょこがジェスチャーしてくからちゃんと答えてくれるかな？
Now Subaru, I'm going to perform gestures. Will you answer correctly?
オッケー！
Okay!
レッツゴー！レッツゴー！
Let's go! Let's go!
ちょこ先生もっと真ん中の方がいいんじゃない？なんかスバルど真ん中にいるんだけど。
Choco-sensei, shouldn't you be more in the center? For some reason, I'm right in the middle.
はい、じゃあね、これからね、それでは早速始めていきたいと思います。
Alright, now... well, I'd like to get started right away.
まず第1のお題。
First, the first theme...
おっ！
Oh!
3、2、1、ACT！
3, 2, 1, ACT!
来い！
Bring it!
バスケ？
Basketball?
チューリップ？
Tulip?
何それ？
What is that?
妖怪？妖怪？
A yokai? A yokai?
沼に引きずり落とそうとしてくる妖怪じゃん！
It's a yokai trying to drag someone into a swamp!
何それ？
What is that?
何それ！？
What is that!?
何これ、えっ？
What is this, eh?
あれ？
Huh?
あの、うわっ！
Um, whoa!
パンツでさ、何それ？
With pants, what's that?
猫？猫？
A cat? A cat?
何何何！？もっと別の動きして！別の動き！
What what what!? Do some other movement! Other movement!
なー、一緒じゃねえか！
Hey, it's the same thing!
平泳ぎ？平泳ぎ？平泳ぎ？
Breaststroke? Breaststroke? Breaststroke?
水泳？
Swimming?
えっ、これ...
Eh, this...
妖怪じゃねえか！
It's just a yokai!
猫、猫、猫！
Cat, cat, cat!
何、何！？
What, what!?
カエル？
A frog?
カエルじゃん...
It's a frog...
えっ、何これ？猫じゃないの、猫じゃ。
Eh, what's this? Is it not a cat? It's a cat.
猫じゃない？
Not a cat?
分かってねえ...
I don't get it...
何？何を打ち上げてんだよ。
What? What are you launching?
花火、花火、花火！
Fireworks, fireworks, fireworks!
分かってねえな、スバル...
You don't get it, Subaru...
し、しらねーよ、お前！
I-I don't know, you!
ま、待てよ、お前！
W-wait up, you!
分かってねえな、スバル...
You don't get it, Subaru...
し、しらねーよ、お前...
I-I don't know, you...
これしかねーだろ、お前！
This is all it could be, you!
何それ？
What is that?
えっ、トトロ？
Eh, Totoro?
ほら！
Look!
あと5秒しかないよ、スバル。
Only 5 seconds left, Subaru.
いやいや、待て待て、お前...
No no, wait wait, you...
お前いい加減な動きすんのやめろマジで。
Stop making such vague movements, seriously.
これしかねーんだよ！
This is the only thing it can be!
何なんだよ、それ！
What the heck is that!
何それ？
What is that?
答えは...
The answer is...
え、分かんない？みんなも。
Eh, you don't know? Everyone else too.
分かんねえから今待ってんだよ、これ...
I don't know, so I'm waiting right now...
答えは、噴水です！
The answer is... a fountain!
答え 噴水
Answer: Fountain
いや待て待て待て待て...
No, wait wait wait wait...
噴水のその上は分かんだよ、でもさ...
I get the top part of the fountain, but...
その下のさ、猫っぽい動きは何なの？
What's with that cat-like movement at the bottom?
口から「あー」って出て...
It comes out of the mouth like "aaa"...
お前それマーライオンじゃねえか！マーライオン！
That's a Merlion! A Merlion!
ややこしすぎるんだけど！
That's way too confusing!
これで分かるべきだったね。
You should've known by this.
あ、分からねえだろ、それじゃあ...
Ah, there's no way I'd know from that...
デジャヴかよ、お前...
Is this deja vu, you...
まぁこんな感じか。
Well, something like that.
そうそうそう。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
これちなみにスバルはコメント見てていいの？
By the way, is it okay if Subaru looks at the comments?
え？
Eh?
コメント欄に助けを求めるんですか？スバル様。
Are you asking the comment section for help, Subaru-sama?
いや、お前自分のジェスチャーのクオリティを見返してから言えマジで！
No, look back at the quality of your own gestures before you say that, seriously!
分かったね、じゃあ見ない、見ないようにします。見ないようにね。
Understood, then I won't look, I'll try not to look. I won't look.
あ、ね。
Ah, right.
分かった。
Got it.
次何だったかな...おけおけ。
What was next... Okay, okay.
行こう。
Let's go.
行こうじゃねーよ。
Don't "Let's go" me.
第2問！
Question 2!
行きます！
Here I go!
はい、どうぞ。
Yes, go ahead.
3、2、1、ACT！
3, 2, 1, ACT!
え？マリン船長、マリン船長！
Eh? Captain Marine, Captain Marine!
ブリっ子。
Acting cute.
できません、そんなこと！
I can't do that!
できません！
I can't!
怖い怖い！
Scary, scary!
不審者にあったチョコ先生？何これ...
Choco-sensei meeting a suspicious person? What is this...
できません！
I can't!
船長じゃねえかよ、それ！
That's the Captain!
え？
Eh?
もっと他に、もっと他に動きちょうだい！
Something else, give me some other movement!
何？何を履いたの今？
What? What did you just put on?
ミニスカート、ミニスカート！
Mini skirt, mini skirt!
見えそうで見えない...
Peeking but not peeking...
何？その動き何なの、それ！
What? What's with that movement!
トイレ、トイレに行きたいけど行けない人！
Someone who wants to go to the toilet but can't!
何？え？
What? Eh?
ストップ！
Stop!
いやいやいやいや、分かんねえ！
No no no no, I don't know!
え、これ私間違い、あれ？
Eh, did I make a mistake, huh?
何？ストップ！
What? Stop!
いやいやいやいや...え、あれ...
No no no no... eh, that...
ピンク・レディー？
Pink Lady?
え、何？
Eh, what?
船長じゃないの、これ？
Isn't this the Captain?
ケツ、フリフリ！
Ass wiggling!
さぁスバル、最終的な答えは...
Well Subaru, the final answer...
何でしょう？
is what?
お答えください。
Please answer.
トイレに行きたいマリン船長！分かんねえ！
Captain Marine wanting to go to the bathroom! I don't know!
途中までは合ってたのに。
It was correct up until the middle part.
え、途中まで合ってるの？
Eh, it was correct up until the middle?
途中までは合ってたのに。
It was correct up until the middle part.
え、じゃあトイレに行きたいが合ってるの？
Eh, so the "wanting to go to the toilet" part was right?
ちゃうちゃう。トイレ行きたいんじゃない。
No, no. I wasn't trying to say I want to go to the toilet.
正解は言ってたんだよ。
I already said the correct answer.
え？
Eh?
正解は、ナルシストのぶりっ子でした。
The answer was "Narcissistic girl who acts cute".
答え ナルシストのぶりっ子
Answer: Narcissistic girl who acts cute
残りの3問、正解しないと食べられなくなっちゃう。
If you don't get the remaining three right, you won't be able to eat.
分かるわけねーだろ！これふんわりしすぎだろ！分かるわけねーだろ！
There's no way I'd know! This is too vague! There's no way I'd know!
お前そんなデスゲームでいいのかよ！お前はデスゲーマーの風上にも置けねえやつだ！
Is that kind of death game okay with you?! You're a disgrace to death gamers!
分かった分かった。
Okay, okay.
でも、残り3問は、分かりやすくしてあげるよ。しょうがないな。
But for the remaining three questions, I'll make them easier. Can't be helped.
えーやったー！やったねやったね！
Eh, yay! We did it, we did it!
それでは3問目。
Now for the third question.
3、2、1、アクト！
3, 2, 1, act!
あ、ちょこ先生どうした？
Ah, what's wrong, Choco-sensei?
待って。私3問目どっちでしたっけ。確かこっち。
Wait. Which one was the third question? Pretty sure it was this one.
ねえ、しっかりしてちょこ先生！
Hey, get it together, Choco-sensei!
ジェットコースター！ジェットコースター！
Jet coaster! Jet coaster!
いや、待て、これが...
No, wait, this is...
正解！
Correct!
きたきたきたきた！
Here it comes, here it comes!
正解はジェットコースターでしたー！
The answer was "Jet coaster"!
答え ジェットコースター
Answer: Jet coaster
マジでね、登山家とで迷ったんだよ。
Seriously, I was torn between that and a mountain climber.
登山してるおばあちゃんと迷ったんだよ、お前。
I was torn with an old lady climbing a mountain.
最初重いリュック背負ってただろ！おむすびころりんの動きだっただろそれ！
At first you were carrying a heavy backpack, right?! That was the movement from "Omusubi Kororin"!
どう見てもアクトが下手すぎるだろマジで！
No matter how you look at it, your acting is too bad, seriously!
お前、穴にむすび落としてんじゃねーよ！
Don't drop the rice ball into the hole!
何よ！落としたんスバルじゃねーわ！お前だわどちらかと言うと。
What?! It's not like I dropped it, Subaru! If anything, it was you.
続いて第4問目。
Moving on to the fourth question.
3、2、1、アクト！
3, 2, 1, act!
ピヨピヨピヨピヨ...
Piyo piyo piyo piyo...
おっと、何かがある。
Oh, something's happening.
うわっ、足が！足が！足がやられた！
Whoa, my leg! My leg! My leg is hurt!
もう僕のことは置いていってほしいピヨ。
I want you to leave me behind, piyo.
ピヨ！何これ？
Piyo! What is this?
飛べない、飛べない。飛べない鳥はただの鳥。
Can't fly, can't fly. A bird that can't fly is just a bird.
アヒル、アヒル、アヒル！ニワトリ！
Duck, duck, duck! Chicken!
ピヨ、ピヨ、ピヨ、ピヨ...
Piyo, piyo, piyo, piyo...
ペンギン！ペンギン！
Penguin! Penguin!
息が絶え絶え、何それ？ダチョウ、ダチョウ！
Out of breath, what's that? Ostrich, ostrich!
ダチョウじゃない。
It's not an ostrich.
え、何何？行進？
Eh, what what? Marching?
ヒントヒントヒント！
Hint hint hint!
ひよこ、ひよこ、ニワトリ！どうだ！歩いているひよこ、ニワトリ、アヒル！
Chick, chick, chicken! How's that! A walking chick, chicken, duck!
それでは、正解をどうぞ。
Well then, please give the answer.
正解は、アヒルでしたー！
The answer was "Duck"!
答え アヒル
Answer: Duck
よっしゃー！私正解してんのに何でお前ピンポン鳴らさねえんだよと思ってたよ！
Yesss! I was thinking "I got it right, why didn't you sound the buzzer!"!
ジャッジ甘いぞこれ！ジャッジ！お前あとで概要欄名前変えとけよマジで！
The judging is weak! Judge! You seriously change your name in the description later!
やっぱりスバルじゃねーか。
It was Subaru after all.
じゃあ最後の問題に参りましょうか。
Well then, shall we move on to the last question?
それでは、最後の問題でございます。
Now then, for the final question.
にーにー、えちち、あくと、あくと！
Nee-nee, etiti, akuto, akuto!
頑張れ、チョコ先！
Go for it, Choco-sen!
宝鐘マリン船長！あはははは！
Captain Houshou Marine! Ahahaha!
お！チョコ先終わったよ！
Oh! Choco-sen, you're finished!
ちょっとまだやり足りない？マリン船長まだやり足りない？
Do you still want to do more? Are you not satisfied with Marine-sencho?
宝鐘マリンです！イヤァァァ！
I'm Houshou Marine! Iyaaaa!
これ馬鹿怒られるからやめよう、マジこれ馬鹿怒られるから本当に！
I'll get really scolded for this, so I'll stop. Seriously, I'll get scolded!
答え：宝鐘マリン
Answer: Houshou Marine
はい！ということで、答えはマリン船長でした！
Yes! So, the answer was Captain Marine!
あれ？チョコ先これ…
Wait, Choco-sen, this...
ということでね、スバル、ジェスチャーゲーム、死にそうやんお前！
Anyway, Subaru... the gesture game... you look like you're dying!
はい！ということでスバル様、ちょっとこっち来て？
Alright! Anyway, Subaru-sama, come over here for a bit?
あ、ありがと！元に戻してくれるの？
Ah, thanks! You're going to put me back to normal?
スバル、おいでこっち。元にちょっと…スバル、バックでしか歩行できないから！ちょっとね、まだこの身体慣れてないんだよ！
Subaru, come here. Wait... Subaru can only walk backwards! I'm not used to this body yet!
スバルの姿、元の姿に戻してくん、チョコ先！
Put me back into my original Subaru form, Choco-sen!
わかった、わかった。
Got it, got it.
ありがと、ありがと！
Thanks, thanks!
スバル、おいで。
Subaru, come here.
ありがと、ありがと！やっぱりチョコ先生は優しいんだなぁ！
Thanks, thanks! Choco-sensei is so kind after all!
さてと、まあこれでね、食材調達もできたことだし、早速料理していきましょうかね！
Well then, now that we've got the ingredients, let's go and cook right away!
え？ほら、スバル、おいで。
Eh? Come on, Subaru, come here.
あ、じゃあ皆さん！スバル、じゃあまたね！ありがとうございます！お邪魔しました！
Ah, everyone! Subaru will... see you later! Thank you! Sorry for intruding!
みんな、また後でね！あ！すり抜けていく！バイバイ！
Everyone, see you later! Ah! I'm phasing through! Bye bye!
よしよし、スバル、可愛いねぇ。わいわい！今日どこ行くの？今日どこ行くの？
Alright, alright, Subaru, you're so cute. Yay! Where are we going today? Where are we going today?
今日は魔界の遊園地行くのよ、スバル。
We're going to the Underworld Amusement Park today, Subaru.
遊園地！いいねいいね！
Amusement park! Nice, nice!
いや、魔界の遊園地といえばね、なんと目玉は…お化け屋敷！
Well, speaking of the Underworld Amusement Park... the main attraction is... the Ghost Mansion!
おぉー！いいねいいね！お化け屋敷！いいねいいね！
Ohhh! Nice, nice! Ghost mansion! Nice, nice!
スバルもお化けになってみたい？
Subaru, do you want to try being a ghost too?
あ！驚かす側ってこと？いいね！
Ah! You mean the one who scares people? Nice!
うん！じゃあお化けになってもらいたいか、スバルは…
Yeah! Well then, I want Subaru to become a ghost...
お化け役やってみたい！
I want to try being a ghost!
じゃあチョコがその願い叶えてあげましょう！ちょっと待って危ない危ない、それは危ない、そのテンションで言うことじゃない、それはチョコ先！
Then Choco will grant that wish! Wait, hold on, that's dangerous. That's not something you say with that tone, Choco-sen!
落ち着いてチョコ先マジで！何言ってるのスバル、
Seriously, calm down Choco-sen! What are you saying, Subaru?
いやいや危なすぎだろそれ…だってお化けになりたいんでしょ？チョコがだったら叶えてあげるわよ！
No no, that's way too dangerous... But you wanted to be a ghost, right? Then Choco will grant your wish!
ちょっ…お前やめっ！せーの、へい！
Wait... stop it! One, two, hey!
あぶあぶあぶあぶあぶあぶ！ちょっ…お前やっちゃっ…お前やっちゃってるよお前！アッジェジェ！嘘だろ、な、な、な！
Whoa whoa whoa! Wait... you're actually doing it! You're actually doing it! Ow ow ow! No way, wait, wait, wait!
嘘ね、うん、なんかスバル…危な危なーい来てたわ。
Oh well. Subaru... that was dangerous.
羽毛一枚抜けたぐらいだったわ。
It was only about one feather that came off.
一枚どころじゃねーよお前！
It wasn't just one feather, you!
死者数増やしてんじゃねーよ！まあまあ、そのプリケツこっちに向けなスバル。やってやるよ！いや無理無理無理無理！
Don't increase the number of deaths! Now, now, turn that plump butt this way, Subaru. I'll do it! No, no, no!
ほら、せーの！無理やめてやめてやめて！あぶねーな！
Here, one, two! No, stop it, stop it! Whoa, that was close!
もう、これ使えないわね、もう。
Man, I can't use this one anymore.
使えないじゃねーんだよお前、そんなことしてるから胸がなおさら減るんだよお前！
What do you mean 'can't use'!? That's why your chest is shrinking even more!
え、じゃあこれ取ったらいい？
Eh, then can I take this?
いやそれはやめてください危ねーから、マジでいろんな意味で危ねーから！
No, please stop that, it's dangerous! Seriously, in many ways!
わかった、じゃあほらスバル、何も持ってないからこっちおいで。
Alright, then look, Subaru, I don't have anything, so come over here.
本当？ほら、ないよ。しょうがないな、まあ誕生日だしね、信じてやるよ二期生の絆！
Really? Look, I don't. Well, it can't be helped, it's your birthday after all. I'll believe in our 2nd gen bond!
可愛いねスバル。二期生の絆だもんね！あ、チョコ先生！そうだよ、ほらこっちおいで。うん。
You're cute, Subaru. Our 2nd gen bond! Ah, Choco-sensei! That's right, come over here. Yeah.
いいよ。ちょっと優しくしてね、ちょっと優しく置いて？
Okay. Be a bit gentle, okay? Put me down gently?
せーの、えい！なんか固いな。ちょっと…ねえ！何やってんの！？
One, two, hey! It's a bit hard. Wait... hey! What are you doing!?
チョコね、あの今日は北京ダック食べるって決めてたの。
Choco, you know, decided to eat Peking Duck today.
いやいやいや待って待って待って！あっちっちっちっ！ごめんね！
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait! It's hot, hot, hot! Sorry!
当たり前だろ！やめてんじゃねーんだよ、お前サイコパスか？マジで！
Of course it is! I'm not telling you to stop, are you a psychopath? Seriously!
まあまあ、スバル、よしよしよしよし。お誕生日おめでとう！
There, there, Subaru. Good girl. Happy Birthday!
ありがと、スバル。
Thank you, Subaru.
て、あれ？スバル？スバル？
Wait, eh? Subaru? Subaru?
スバル？もしかして…
Subaru? Maybe...
ね、ちょっと…こういう時は知ってるわよチョコ。人工呼吸をすれば生き返るって。じゃあ早速…
Wait... in times like this, Choco knows what to do. If I do mouth-to-mouth resuscitation, you'll come back to life. Well then...
うわぁぁぁぁ！やめてやめてやめてやめて！ちょっと待って待って待って！チョコ先ニンニクの匂いもすごいしあと何かあの…
Uwahhhh! Stop it, stop it! Wait, wait, wait! Choco-sen, your breath smells like garlic and something...
スバルの人工呼吸とかは大丈夫です。
Subaru's artificial respiration is fine.
何言ってんの、スバル。大丈夫よ？
What are you saying, Subaru? You'll be fine, right?
ほら、でしょ？
See? Right?
いや、無理無理。ちょっと気合入れるために食べただけだから。
No, no, impossible. I just ate it to fire myself up.
いや、気合入れるためにニンニクを食うな...
No, you ate garlic to fire yourself up...
ほら、うるさいわよ口が。
See, your mouth is so noisy.
ほら。
There.
うぇえええええええ！！
Waaaaaaah!!
はい、ということでね、
Yes, and so,
皆様、スバ虐はいかがだったでしょうか？
everyone, how was the Subaru-harassment?
まあね、まあスバルちょっと炙ったぐらいだから大丈夫なんですけど。
Well, I just roasted Subaru a bit, so it's fine.
そう、北京ダックはね、やっぱローストしないといけないから。
Yes, Peking duck has to be roasted, after all.
まあこの後どうなったのかは皆様のご想像にお任せいたします。
Well, I'll leave what happened after this to your imagination.
ということでね、まあ美味しく頂いたところで、
So, now that we've had a delicious meal,
なんかね、運営さんがちょこのためにケーキをね、用意して頂いたみたいで、
It seems the management prepared a cake for Choco.
ちょっとデザートにケーキを食べようかなって思います。
I think I'll have some cake for dessert.
出でよ、ケーキ！
Come out, cake!
わっ！待って、ちょこ、ちょこ、ちょこ、ちょこ...ちょっと待って。
Whoa! Wait, Choco, Choco, Choco... wait a minute.
や、めっちゃデカい。
Wow, it's huge.
おー...大きい！美味しそう！
Ooh... it's big! Looks delicious!
それでは、ちょこのお誕生日頂きます！
Well then, I'll enjoy my birthday cake!
おいしょーっと！
Heave-ho!
ちょっと待ったー！
Wait a second!
うぇ？
Huh?
ダメだよ、ちょこ先生。
That's no good, Choco-sensei.
メル様？
Mel-sama?
はい、魔界の天才ヴァンパイア、夜空メルだよ！
Yes, the genius vampire from the underworld, it's Yozora Mel!
な、何がダメなんですかメル様？
Wh-what is no good, Mel-sama?
ちょこ先生、えー、お誕生日まずはおめでとうございます。
Choco-sensei, first of all, happy birthday.
あー、メル様ありがとうー！
Ah, thank you Mel-sama!
でも、ケーキを食べるのはメルとの勝負に勝ってからにしてね。
But, you can only eat the cake after you win the battle against Mel.
ガッチ？
For real?
ガッチ！
For real!
目の前にあるのに...
Even though it's right in front of me...
我慢、我慢。
Patience, patience.
メル様の頼みならしょうがないなあ。
If it's Mel-sama's request, I guess I have no choice.
ちょっと元戻しとこ。
I'll put it back for a bit.
メルから、勝負をね、持ち掛けたいと思うんだけど、
Mel would like to challenge you to a battle,
いいかな？
is that okay?
もちろん！
Of course!
まあメル様の勝負なら楽勝で勝っちゃうと思うんでね。
Well, if it's a battle against Mel-sama, I think I'll win easily.
ん、じゃあ勝負のルール説明をするね。
Alright, then I'll explain the rules of the battle.
今から3つのシチュエーションを準備します。
I've prepared three situations.
はい。
Yes.
そのシチュエーションに合ったセリフをメルが言うので、
Mel will say a line that fits that situation,
そのセリフに合わせてちょこ先生は身振り手振り動いてください。
and Choco-sensei, please act it out with gestures.
もう任せてほしいわそれは。
Oh, leave it to me.
3つやってみて、見ているみんなをドキドキさせることができたらちょこ先生の勝ち。
Do all three, and if you can make everyone's hearts race, Choco-sensei wins.
ドキドキさせる。
Make their hearts race.
なるほどね、うんうん。
I see, I see.
ドキドキさせることができたらケーキ食べていいよ。
If you can make their hearts race, you can eat the cake.
ガッチ？ え、頑張る！
For real? I'll do my best!
だから頑張ってね。
So do your best, okay.
任せてほしいわ。
Leave it to me.
メルの無茶振りにちゃんと対応できるかな？
I wonder if she can handle Mel's unreasonable requests.
いやーもうメルキスの絆見せてあげましょうよ、メル様。
No, let's show them the bond of MelKiss, Mel-sama.
そうだね。
That's right.
よし、じゃあ早速一つ目のシチュエーション行ってみよっか。
Alright, let's start with the first situation.
はーい。
Okay.
シチュエーション、ワン！
Situation one!
ワンワン！ お、変わった！ 変わった！
Woof woof! Oh, it changed! It changed!
あ、あー！
Ah, ah!
バレンタインに告白をするシチュエーション
Confessing on Valentine's Day situation
シチュエーション・ワンは、バレンタインに告白をするシチュエーションです。
Situation one is the situation of confessing on Valentine's Day.
いやーこれはドキドキやね。
Wow, this is heart-racing.
ね、ドキドキだね。
Right, it's heart-racing.
なるほどね。
I see.
メル様が告白セリフを言うからちょこは、
Mel-sama will say the confession line, so Choco,
メル様が言っているように、ちょこが言っているように動けばいいってことね。
should move as if Mel-sama is talking, as if Choco is talking.
そう！
Yes!
じゃあ任せてよ。
Then leave it to me.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
いやーメルキスの息合わせてあげますよ、もう、ちょこが。任せてほしいわ。
I'll match the timing of MelKiss. Leave it to me.
分かった、じゃあ早速、ちょこ先生の告白をするバレンタインシチュエーション、
Understood. Then, let's start Choco-sensei's Valentine's confession situation.
行きます！
Here we go!
あの...急に呼び出してごめんね。
Um... sorry for calling you out so suddenly.
えっとね、今日さ、バレンタイン...
Um, you see, today is Valentine's...
バレンタインデーでしょ？
It's Valentine's Day, right?
だから、その...
So, you see...
チョコを作ってきたの。
I made some chocolates.
え？ちょっとちょっと...
Eh? Wait, wait...
誰がチョコだけにチョコレートよ。
Who gives 'Choco' chocolates?
ダジャレじゃないんだから。
It's not a pun!
もう、バカ。
Geez, stupid.
一応言っておくけど、
Just so you know...
これ、義理じゃないんだからね。
this isn't 'courtesy' chocolate, okay?
本命、よ。
It's 'honmei' (true love).
チョコの気持ち、受け取ってくれる？
Will you accept Choco's feelings?
あなたのことが好きです。
I like you.
付き合ってください。
Please go out with me.
やっとー！や、メルの方がちょっとドキドキしちゃった。
Finally! Mel was getting so nervous!
これは... これはチョコの心臓がもたないよー！
This... this is too much for Choco's heart!
や、メルはね、あくまでチョコ先生の気持ちを今、代弁してるだけなの。
Mel was just speaking Choco-sensei's feelings for her.
なるほどね。
I see.
メル様の破壊力がすごいのよ。
Mel-sama's destructive power is amazing.
恥ずかしいよ、メルも。
Mel is embarrassed too.
どうかな、みんなドキドキしてますか？
How was it? Is everyone's heart racing?
ドキドキしてんのかなー。
I wonder if your hearts are racing.
してんのかなー。
I wonder.
メルじゃなくてチョコ先生からのチョコレートなんだね。
These are chocolates from Choco-sensei, not Mel.
チョコレート、みんなもらいました？ちゃんと。
Did everyone receive their chocolates?
もらえたかな？もらえたかな？
Did you get them? Did you?
じゃあ、続いてシチュエーション２！２！２！
Next, Situation 2! Two! Two!
２もドキドキさせることができますかね？
Can Situation 2 make hearts race too?
や、できるかなー！
I wonder if we can!
せっかくだからね、ノリノリにしたいから、
If we're doing this, I want to do it properly...
ちょっとチョコのマイクはオフでお願いしますね、やってる最中は。
Please turn off Choco's mic while we're doing it.
じゃあメル様、お願いします。
Mel-sama, please.
はい、シチュエーション２はチョコ先生がなんと告白をされるシチュエーションになります。
Yes, Situation 2 is Choco-sensei getting confessed to!
屋上じゃん。
On the rooftop!
いやー、これはドキドキするね、チョコ屋上で告白されんの？
Oh, this is heart-racing! Choco getting confessed to on the rooftop!
じゃあ、行きますよ。
Okay, here we go.
はい。
Yes.
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
ええ、もう今日のお仕事は...
Well, my work for today...
終わってるわよ。
...is already finished.
ちょ、チョコ先生のマイク入ってるみたい。
Wait, Choco-sensei's mic seems to be on.
あーなるほどね！
Oh, I see!
あの、配信には載せないでほしいです。お願いします。
Please don't include this in the stream. Please.
めっ、ですよ。
I'm watching you!
じゃ、はい、もう一回行きます。
Okay, one more time.
ポン！
Pon!
あら、どうしたの？
Oh? What's wrong?
こんなところに呼び出して、
Calling me to a place like this...
何か相談事かしら？
do you have something to discuss?
ええ、もう今日のお仕事は終わってるわよ。
Well, my work for today is already finished.
うーん、なんだか様子が変ね。
Hmm... something seems off.
お顔もなんだか赤いし、
Your face is a bit red too...
熱でもあるの？
do you have a fever?
保健室のベッド空いてるから、
The nurse's office bed is open,
少し休む？
do you want to rest for a bit?
え？
Eh?
これ、チョコレート？
Is this... chocolate?
チョコにくれるの？
Are you giving it to Choco?
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
でもどうして？
But why?
まあ、嬉しいわ。
Well, I'm happy.
バレンタインデーだものね。
It is Valentine's Day, after all.
ねえ、これってどういう意味かしら？
Hey, what does this mean?
本命チョコ、って
Can I take this as
受け取ってもいいのかな？
'honmei' chocolate?
本命？
Honmei?
チョコも...
Choco, too...
ホワイトデーで
On White Day...
期待していてね
...please look forward to it.
カーン！カーン！カーン！
Clang! Clang! Clang!
どうでした？どうでした？どうでした？
How was it? How was it? How was it?
どうだったかな～
I wonder how it was...
まさかのバレンタインデーに告白をされるっていうね
I didn't expect to get confessed to on Valentine's Day.
逆チョコじゃん
It was a "reverse chocolate" situation.
いや、ちょっとガチ恋距離やばかったね、今
Man, that "serious love distance" was insane just now.
ね、ちょっとなんかドキドキしちゃうよ
Right? It made my heart race a bit.
もうメル様の声と合わさったらドキドキしちゃうよ、もう
Combined with Mel-sama's voice, my heart was pounding!
ちょっとメルもね、チョコ先生の動きを見てドキドキしてたけど
Mel was also heart-thumping watching Choco-sensei's movements.
ガチ？みんなもっとドキドキしてるんじゃないかな
Really? I think everyone else's hearts are racing even more.
これはどうかな、次で最後？
I wonder... Is the next one the last?
そうだね、次で最後になります
That's right, the next one will be the last.
もっとメル様と一緒にいたいんだけどな、チョコ
Choco wants to be with Mel-sama more, though...
でも今日は特別な日だから
But today is a special day.
わかった。終わったら二人でいようね
Understood. Let's be together after this is over.
わかった、頑張る
Okay, I'll do my best!
じゃあ、次のシチュエーション、シチュエーション3！
Well then, the next situation, situation 3!
ラスト！ラスト！ラスト！
The last! The last! The last!
テレン！「バレンタインに告白を見守る」シチュエーションです
Ta-da! It's the "Watching a Valentine confession" situation.
です！見守る... 見守る？
Yes! Watching... watching?
なるほど、覗いてんの？
I see, so you're peeping?
ガチ？
Seriously?
見守るでも色んなシチュエーションがあるからね
Well, "watching" can mean many different things.
あ、こういう感じなのね、オッケーオッケー
Ah, so it's like this. Okay, okay.
準備はいいですか？
Are you ready?
任せてほしい
Leave it to me.
よし、じゃあ告白を見守るチョコ先生まで
Alright, then, "Choco-sensei watching a confession" in...
3, 2, 1
カーン！
Clang!
よいしょ... よいしょ...
Heave-ho... heave-ho...
あらあら、まあまあ。あそこにいるのは金髪のエルフ？
My, my. Is that a blonde elf over there?
と、銀髪の騎士？
And a silver-haired knight?
お、女子高生が二人いるわね
Oh, there are two high school students.
もう、何してるのかしら
Gosh, I wonder what they're doing.
もう少し近づいてみましょう
Let's get a bit closer.
よいしょ...
Heave-ho...
あれはチョコレートかしら
Is that... chocolate?
あっそっか、今日はバレンタインデーだものね
Ah, that's right. Today is Valentine's Day.
待って、あれは友チョコなの？それとも本命チョコ？
Wait, is that "friendship chocolate" or "true love chocolate"?
どっちなの？
Which is it?
ちょっと待って、会話が聞き取れないじゃない
Hold on, I can't hear their conversation.
もっともっと近づかなきゃ
I have to get closer and closer.
バレないように...
So I don't get caught...
そーっと... そーっと...
Stealthily... stealthily...
ドッカーン！
Kaboom!
あ、バレた... バレてないよね？
Ah, I'm spotted... No, I'm not, right?
でももう、もどかしいわね。早くチョコレート渡しなさいよ！
But gosh, this is so frustrating. Just give him the chocolate already!
もう！そこの二人！
Geez! You two over there!
どう考えても両想いなんだから、さっさとお互いのチョコレート、交換しなさい！
It's obvious you both like each other, so just exchange your chocolates already!
あ...
Ah...
やべ、バレちゃった
Oops, I got caught.
はい、ということで、皆様いかがだったでしょうか
So, there you have it. Everyone, how was that?
いや、めちゃおもろいな、この企画
Man, this segment is super funny.
なんかチョコ先生らしかったね、ちょっと
That was very "Choco-sensei-like," wasn't it?
ガチ？
Really?
うん、いやでもわかる。チョコもよくサプライズしようと思ってやるんだけど、結構バレること多い
Yeah. I get it. Choco often tries to do surprises, but I get caught pretty often.
そうなの？
Is that so?
「聞こえない聞こえない」と思って、なんか準備してるじゃん
Like, I'm thinking "they can't hear me," and I'm preparing something...
もう準備し終わって、いつ出ていこうかなってタイミングを見計らうのよ
I've finished preparing, and I'm just waiting for the right moment to come out.
タイミング見計らおうと思ってドア開けようとした瞬間に、そのサプライズ相手がドア開けちゃって、「あ... バレちゃった」みたいな
And just as I'm about to open the door to time it perfectly, the target of the surprise opens it first. "Ah... I'm caught."
こと多い、結構
That happens quite a lot, actually.
そっか、バレても嬉しいもんね
I see. Well, it's still nice even if you get caught.
そう、嬉しい。でもね、メル様とね...
Yeah, it's nice. But you know, with Mel-sama...
やるわね！
Not bad!
うん、メルも誘ってくれてありがと！
Yeah, thanks for inviting Mel too!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
それじゃあね、みんなドキドキ...
Well then, everyone's heart is pounding...
コメント見る限りね、みんなドキドキしていたようなので...
From what I can see in the comments, it seems everyone was nervous...
ご褒美として、ちょこ先生、ケーキ食べていいよ！
As a reward, Choco-sensei, you can eat some cake!
やったー！
Yay!
おー、どうぞ！
Oh, here you go!
いっぱい、いっぱい召し上がれ！
Eat as much as you like!
食べちゃうよ、食べちゃうよ！
I'm gonna eat it, I'm gonna eat it!
食べて！
Eat up!
いでよ、フォーク！
Come forth, fork!
フォーク！
Fork!
ていっ！ていっ！
Tei! Tei!
あ、きたきた。
Oh, it's here.
いただきまーす！
Bon appetit!
おー、美味しそう。
Oh, looks delicious.
美味しい、美味しいよ、メル様！
It's delicious, it's delicious, Mel-sama!
良かったー。
I'm glad.
うん... まあね。
Yeah... Well.
でも実はね、ちょっとちょことメル様ね...
But actually, Choco and Mel-sama...
みんなにこのケーキだけじゃなくて、バレンタインプレゼントがあるんですよ。
we have a Valentine's present for everyone, not just this cake.
あ、そうだね！
Ah, that's right!
ちょっと言っちゃう？
Should we say it?
実はね...
Actually...
言っちゃおう、メル様！
Let's say it, Mel-sama!
言っちゃおうか！
Should we!
ということで...
And so...
ちょことメル様からのバレンタインプレゼントはこちら！
The Valentine's present from Choco and Mel-sama is this!
こちらだ！
It's this!
スイートマジック
Sweet Magic
じゃんじゃじゃーん！
Tada!
この後、この3D放送が終わった22時から...
After this, from 22:00 when this 3D broadcast ends...
なんと！初めての！
Surprisingly! For the first time!
初めての！
First time!
メルティキス、歌ってみた公開！
Melty Kiss 'tried singing' cover release!
ずっと言ってたもんね。
We've been saying it for a long time.
そう、やりたいねやりたいねって言ってたんだけど、なかなかね、ちょっと忙しくてできなかったんだけど。
Yeah, we kept saying we wanted to do it, but we were a bit busy and couldn't.
今回ね、そう、メル様「スイートマジック歌いたいよ」って言ったらね、メル様「いいよ」って言ってくれて。
But this time, when I told Mel-sama I wanted to sing Sweet Magic, she said okay.
ね、一緒に歌おうねって言って今回、そう、実現いたしました！
We said let's sing together, and this time, it came true!
うぇーい！
Yay!
いや、とってもね、イラストも動画もね、可愛い感じに仕上がってるので。
The illustrations and video turned out really cute.
ぜひぜひ、この後22時からよろしくお願いします。
So please look forward to it from 22:00.
皆様ぜひぜひ聞いてみてください。
Everyone, please give it a listen.
絶対見てね！
Be sure to watch!
見てね！
Watch it!
それと...
And also...
あともう一つ！
One more thing!
おー！
Oh!
- ギミチョコ！！ - GIMME CHOCOLATE!! BABY METAL
- Gimme Chocolate!! - GIMME CHOCOLATE!! BABY METAL
てれん、てれーん！
Tada!
おー！
Oh!
ま、これはちょこのチャンネルじゃなくて、メル様のチャンネルなのですが。
Well, this isn't on Choco's channel, but on Mel-sama's channel.
もうちょうどね、21時、もう公開されてるのですが。
It's already been released at 21:00.
ギミチョコ、なんとこの3人で歌っちゃいました！
We sang Gimme Chocolate with these three!
歌っちゃいました！やったー！
We sang it! Yay!
メルとちょこ先生はね、あのー何だろうサイドにね、いてわちゃわちゃしてますけど。
Mel and Choco-sensei are on the sides, messing around.
そう、ぜひぜひ、もうめちゃめちゃかっこいいんですよ、この曲。
Yeah, please check it out, this song is super cool.
ね、かっこいいし可愛いしね！
Right, it's cool and cute!
そう！いや、もうちょこね、これはね、出た瞬間ね、送ってもらったの。
Right! I mean, Choco got sent this the moment it came out.
もう「あー！」ってなった。「かっこいい、最高！」と思って。
I was like "Ah!". Thinking "It's so cool, the best!"
そう、ぜひぜひ皆様、ただいまね公開されているので、こちらの方もチェックしてみてください。
So everyone, please check this out as well, since it's currently released.
ください！
Please do!
ということでね。
So with that said.
皆様、ぜひぜひメルティキスよろしくお願いします。
Everyone, please support Melty Kiss.
お願いします。
Please.
と、いうことで、ちょこ先生、改めてお誕生日おめでとう！
So, Choco-sensei, once again, happy birthday!
ありがとー、メル様！
Thank you, Mel-sama!
生まれてきてくれて本当にありがとう。
Thank you so much for being born.
嬉しい、ありがとー！
I'm so happy, thank you!
そろそろメルはね、お邪魔... ん、違う。退散！退散しようと思います。
It's about time for Mel to... no, that's wrong. Depart! I think I'll be taking my leave.
行っちゃうの？
You're leaving?
うん。でも残りの時間もみんなと楽しく過ごしてね！
Yeah. But enjoy the rest of your time with everyone!
わかった。ありがとメル様、また後でね！
Understood. Thanks Mel-sama, see you later!
ありがとう。またね！またねー！
Thank you. See ya! See ya!
ということでね、皆様、ぜひぜひ歌ってみたの方も聞いてみてくださいということで。
So, everyone, please do listen to the cover song as well.
まあね、ケーキも食べて、色々食べたことだし。
Well, since I've eaten the cake and various other things.
まあね、最後はちょこ、こう見えてアイドルなんで。
Well, in the end, Choco is an idol, believe it or not.
アイドルらしくライブ会場に向かいたいと思います！
I'd like to head to the live venue like a true idol!
ライブ会場への道は、ぜひチョコメイト様たちで...
The path to the live venue, I hope you Chocomates...
...彩って頂けたら嬉しいです！
...I'd be happy if you could brighten it up!
なんと今回ね スパチャレッドカーペットと
And this time, with the Super Chat Red Carpet...
普通のスーパーチャットでは
...and regular Super Chats,
今回チョコ、プレゼント募集してなくて
Choco didn't ask for any presents this time,
お手紙だけっていうお誕生日のやつを
and went with a "letters only" birthday instead,
取らせて頂いてたんですけど ぜひここで
but by all means, right here...
そう、めっちゃあったのリプに
Yeah, there were so many replies like,
「チョコ先生なんで手紙だけなの？」みたいな
"Choco-sensei, why only letters?"
「あれ？プレゼント送りたかったのに」みたいな
"Wait, I wanted to send a present!"
ま、ぜひぜひ、皆様、プレゼントもね 頂けたら
So, please, everyone, if I could receive presents too...
ここで頂けたらチョコは嬉しいです！ということで
I'd be happy to receive them here! And so,
それでは レッツ・スタート！
without further ado, let's start!
スパチャおめでとう、ありがとう！
Thank you for the Super Chats!
そうなんです 今回はね
That's right. This time,
みんなにとっておいてって言ったのは
the reason I told everyone to save up,
このためです ありがとう いつも
was for this. Thank you, as always.
そう、久々の3D配信
Yes, it's been a while since my last 3D stream.
皆様いかがでしょうか？
How do you all like it?
運営さん、アップでお願いします
Management, can I get a close-up please?
チョコ先生おめでとうございます
Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます ちょっとチョコの顔面アップでいいですか？
Thank you. Can I get a close-up of Choco's face?
みんな、いつもありがとう
Everyone, thank you for everything.
わあ、すごい
Wow, amazing.
最近ね、ちょっといろいろバタバタしとって
Lately, things have been a bit hectic,
配信頻度が減っちゃってますが
so my streaming frequency has dropped,
これからもね 癒月チョコ 頑張っていこうと思うので
but I'll keep doing my best as Yuzuki Choco,
これからもよろしくお願いします
so I look forward to your continued support.
ありがとう みんな お誕生日おめでとう ありがとう！
Thank you, everyone. Thank you for the birthday wishes!
ありがとう みんな
Thank you, everyone.
それでは
And now,
ライブ会場の方に 行きたいと思います
I'd like to head over to the live performance venue.
ベノム
Venom
作詞/作曲:Kairiki bear(かいりきベア)
Lyrics/Composition: Kairiki bear
足りないものなんだ 僕らの人生
What is missing? Our lives.
正解どこなんだ 僕らの人生
Where is the answer? Our lives.
様せ 様せ ねえ 様せ 様せ
Get sick, get sick, hey, get sick, get sick
あらま 待った待った 霊界 無いな 霊界 無いな 霊界 無いな
Oh my, wait, wait, no spirit world, no spirit world, no spirit world
あ、正味 クソゲーだ 空から あわれ
Ah, honestly it's a kuso-ge, pity from the sky
あ、倦怠モード くだ 僕らの人生
Ah, fatigue mode... our lives
校内モード くだ 鏡よ 鏡
School mode... mirror mirror
様せ 全敗 ない 待った チャイナ 全敗 バイバイ 制裁 ない ない
Get sick, no total defeat, wait, China, total defeat, bye bye, no punishment
あ、後悔モード くだ 笑えよ 笑え
Ah, regret mode... laugh, laugh
心にヒビ 顔興味 ギャンギャン
Cracks in the heart, face interest, gyan gyan
だんだん 強がって ドロドロに 伏す
Gradually acting tough, lying in the mud
毒毒 飲み込んで 苦しんで 泣いて
Swallowing poison, suffering, crying
吐き出せないの ベノ ベノ ベノム
Can't spit it out, veno, veno, venom
さよなら
Goodbye
あらま 求愛中 毒毒 流るる
Oh my, in the middle of courtship, the poison flows
頂戴ね 痛い痛いの とんでけ
Give it to me, pain pain go away
そのガキ 毒毒 こぼるる
In that gap, poison spills
はい はい あらま ベノ ベノ ベノム めっ！
Yes, yes, oh my, veno, veno, venom, BAD!
あ、最高点 ゼロだ 僕らの人生
Ah, the highest score is zero, our lives
断絶テロップ だ 鏡よ 鏡
Disconnected telop... mirror mirror
様せ 脳内 ペケ 待った ローマイ 脳内 ナイナイ 内向 めめ
Get sick, no brain, wait, Roman... no brain, no no, introversion, bad bad
あ、オーバードーズ 消えた あがれよ あがれ
Ah, overdose vanished, rise up, rise up
心の中 ヒビ 無理 オブ 無理 ギャンギャン
Cracks inside the heart, impossible of impossible, gyan gyan
どんどん 強がって バラバラに 伏す
Steadily acting tough, lying in pieces
毒毒 飲み込んで 苦しんで 泣いて
Swallowing poison, suffering, crying
逃げ出せないの ベノ ベノ ベノム
Can't escape, veno, veno, venom
あらま 求愛中 毒毒 流るる
Oh my, in the middle of courtship, the poison flows
頂戴ね 痛い痛いの とんでけ
Give it to me, pain pain go away
そのガキ 毒毒 欲しがる
In that gap, poison wants
はい はい あらま ベノ ベノ ベノム めっ！
Yes, yes, oh my, veno, veno, venom, BAD!
もう 求愛中 毒毒 回るる
Already, in the middle of courtship, poison rotates
頂戴ね 痛い痛いの しくしく
Give it to me, pain pain, sobbing
そんな場所 毒毒 消えるる
In such a place, poison disappears
はい はい はい はい
Yes, yes, yes, yes
求愛中 毒毒 流るる
In the middle of courtship, the poison flows
頂戴ね 痛い痛いの とんでけ
Give it to me, pain pain go away
そのガキ 毒毒 こぼるる
In that gap, poison spills
はい はい あらま ベノ ベノ ベノム
Yes, yes, oh my, veno, veno, venom
あ、ベノ ベノ ベノム
Ah, veno, veno, venom
あ、ベノ ベノ ベノム めっ！
Ah, veno, veno, venom, BAD!
はいということで、
Alright, so,
皆様、いかがだったでしょうか？
everyone, how was it?
ちょっとね、今回は、ちょっとカッコよ目の『ベノム』って曲を歌わせていただきました。
For this time, I sang a slightly cool song called "Venom".
サイリウムもありがとう！
Thank you for the penlights too!
ということでね、ここでちょこ、一つ、告知があります！
So, Choco has one announcement here!
運営さん、お願いしまーす！
Staff, please!
なんと、癒月ちょこ、約半年ぶりに、
To my surprise, Yuzuki Choco, after about half a year,
記念ボイス出します！
is releasing commemorative voices!
ま、これはね、癒月ちょこが全部台本を考えて録音させて頂いて作らせていただきました、
Well, for these, I thought of the scripts, recorded them, and made them myself,
誕生日記念ボイス2021ということでね。今回、比良坂とお先生
as the "Birthday Commemorative Voices 2021". This time, Hirasaka-too-sensei's...
描き下ろしの、おっぱいマウスパッド！とね、
newly drawn "oppai" mousepad! And,
なんと、描き下ろしのポストカード、プラス、
surprise, surprise, a newly drawn postcard, plus,
特典耳舐めボイスの『いただきバレンタイン』が全部セットに付いてくるという、
the bonus ear-licking voice "Itadaki Valentine" comes with the full set,
素晴らしいボイスを、出し、ます！！
such wonderful voices will be released!!
皆様、お待たせいたしました！
Everyone, thank you for waiting!
あれ？ちょこ先生、今回クリスマスとか、
Oh? "Choco-sensei, you didn't release voices for Christmas or..."
あれ？2周年記念でボイス出してないな？って思ったでしょ？
"Oh? You didn't release voices for the 2nd anniversary either?" You thought that, right?
なんと、今回ここにまとめさせていただきました！
Well, I've gathered them all here this time!
ということでね、ぜひぜひ皆様、
So, everyone, please,
概要欄にね、URLが貼ってあるので、BOOTHの方でぜひぜひ。
the URL is in the description, so please check it on BOOTH.
全部セットにはね、全部特典付いてくるのですが、
The full set comes with all the bonuses,
ま、個別だとね、付いてこないのでぜひぜひ全部セットの方、
but they don't come individually, so please consider the full set.
よろしくお願いします！ということでね、
Please support me! And so,
みんな、
everyone,
もう一曲だけ歌っていい？チョコ。
Can Choco sing just one more song?
ねぇねぇねぇねぇ、もう一曲だけ歌っていい？
Hey, hey, hey, hey, can I sing just one more song?
最近チョコがハマってる曲歌ってもいい？
Can I sing a song that Choco's been into lately?
はい！ということで、そう、全部セットの方は期間限定なのでね、ぜひぜひ
Yes! So, the full set is available for a limited time only, so please...
販売中に、販売期間に、ぜひぜひ全部セットお求めいただけたらと思います。
I hope you'll consider getting the full set during the sale period.
耳なめボイスはね、全部セットにしかついてこないで、期間限定なんでよろしくお願いします！
The ear-licking voice is only in the full set and is for a limited time, so please check it out!
ということで！
And so!
それでは、最後の歌、歌っていきたいと思います！
Now, I'm going to sing the final song!
君色に染まる
作詞/作曲:TOKOTOKO(西沢さんP)
Dyed in Your Color
Lyrics/Music: TOKOTOKO (Nishizawa-san P)
期待してすぐに諦めて
Expect, then immediately give up
曖昧な答えに流されては
Washed away by vague answers
自分だけ置いていかれるような
Feeling like I'm the only one left behind
そんなイメージが胸を突つく夜だ
It's a night where such images prick at my heart
覚えてるような
Like I remember
覚えていないような
Like I don't remember
憧れと記憶を彷徨うよ
Wandering between yearnings and memories
僕は君のために
I for you
君は僕のために
You for me
生まれたなら ちょっと嬉しいね
If we were born for each other, I'd be a little happy
気づいたら君色に染まってるような
By the time I realized it, I was dyed in your color
何気ない言葉で汚してほしい
I want you to stain me with casual words
ずっと わからないふりを続けてきたんだ
I've kept pretending not to know all along
この時が来るまで
Until this moment comes
もしかして君と釣り合ってないかな
Maybe I'm not a good match for you?
そんな不安もたまに過ぎるけれど
Such anxieties occasionally cross my mind, but
いつも 困らせてばかりでごめんね
I'm sorry for always causing you trouble
好きだよ 好きだよ 好きだよって伝えたい
I want to tell you "I love you, I love you, I love you"
傷つかないように言葉を探しても
Even if I search for words so as not to get hurt
空回り 気持ちだけ急かされて
Going in circles, only my feelings are being rushed
ねぇ 間違ってるような
Hey, it feels like it's wrong
これで合ってるような
It feels like this is right
二人の答え ずっと よろしくね
Our answer, please keep it this way forever
気づいたら君色に染まってるような
By the time I realized it, I was dyed in your color
何気ない言葉で汚してほしい
I want you to stain me with casual words
ずっと わからないふりを続けてきたんだ
I've kept pretending not to know all along
この時が来るまで
Until this moment comes
もしかして君と釣り合ってないかな
Maybe I'm not a good match for you?
そんな不安もたまに過ぎるけれど
Such anxieties occasionally cross my mind, but
いつも 困らせてばかりでごめんね
I'm sorry for always causing you trouble
好きだよ 好きだよ 好きだよって伝えたい
I want to tell you "I love you, I love you, I love you"
はぁ！メルさんとの歌ってみた、この後プレミア公開なので、よろしくお願いします！
Phew! My song cover with Mel-san will premiere after this, so please check it out!
またねー！
See ya!
重大発表もあるわよ
お誕生日3D配信
There's also a major announcement
Birthday 3D Stream